{"data":[{"question":"Is your father at home? - No, he is away on business. If you have a message for him, I ________ it to him as soon as he ________ home.","a":"give \/ gets","b":"give \/ will get","c":"will give \/ get","d":"will give \/ gets","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Please tell me how to get to the post office? - Go till you ________ to a square with a statue in the middle; then turn left and you ________ it on your right.","a":"come \/ fine","b":"come \/ will find","c":"will come \/ find","d":"will come \/ will find","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Future present tense\/simple present + until\/till \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"What did he say before he left for Paris? - He said he would give me a ring as soon as he ________ Paris.","a":"reaches","b":"reached","c":"will reach","d":"would reach","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple past tense\/future tense in the past+ until\/till \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple past tense tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I thought you were going to the concert. - I was. But when I got there, the tickets ________ sold out. So I ________ go back home.","a":"was \/ had to","b":"had been \/ have to","c":"had been \/ had to","d":"were \/ had to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- When + Simple past tense, simple past continuous\/past perfect tense.\u00a0\n- The whole sentence is past tense- second blank (So I ........... go back home) is in the past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"How long have you been working in this firm? - I have been working here for five years. When I ________ here for fifteen years, I'll be able to get some pension.","a":"work","b":"will be working","c":"has worked","d":"has been working","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense\/future tense + while\/when + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Tell us what ________ to you yesterday?","a":"happen","b":"happened","c":"had happened","d":"has happened","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past (yesterday).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"We ________ you a telegram as soon as we ________ in Chicago tomorrow.","a":"will send \/ arrive","b":"would send \/ arrived","c":"will send \/ will arrive","d":"send \/ arrive","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Future present tense\/simple present + until\/till \/when\/as soon as\/ before + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"The druggist ________ for home when we ________ to the store yesterday.","a":"already left \/ got","b":"had already left \/ got","c":"already left \/ had got","d":"had already left \/ had got","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- We use the past perfect to express the idea that something occurred before another action in the past. \n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Mr. Carlson ________ to another man when I ________ him this morning.","a":"is talking \/ see","b":"was talking \/ saw","c":"had talked \/ saw","d":"has talked \/ saw","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Clause (past continuous) when Clause (past simple): when you say that something happened in the middle of something else in the past","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ Mr. Harris your message when I see him tomorrow.","a":"give","b":"gave","c":"will give","d":"would give","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Future tense\/simple present tense + while\/when + simple present tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}